[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p2_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She's already gone on ahead. Again.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Well, it seems you've found something to capture Morgaine's attention. \\n\\nThat's good because I should like to share with you more about this wondrous place we venture into. Please, follow me…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p4_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We could find useful clues here.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, that is likely; there may even be glyphs in the stonework that will give us hints to the Angry Earth's origins.\\n\\nLet us search, and if you find anything, give a shout, and I will attempt to translate.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p5_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should share this with Morgaine.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, yes, we must. I caught a glimpse of an encampment down the road by the water. Perhaps Morgaine is there. \\n\\nWe should head there directly, if for no other reason than to have a safe place to consider what we've learned.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p6v1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We still don't know what causes the blight.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Exactly, and that is what I will be working on. It seems the sorceress has become distracted with clues about her brother.\\n\\nHelp Morgaine with her search and then meet me in Caliburne, the elder druids' enclave to the north.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p7_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes. We found Myrddin's sanctum in a cave nearby.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "That explains her absence, and it's welcome news! We can delve deeper into the Angry Earth's relationship to Corruption.\\n\\nI'm curious about these druidic rituals used to commune with what they called \"the forest spirit.\"",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p8_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does that mean?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "A plant's hardiness is determined by the dirt encasing its roots, and so do these dryads and other life forms thrive here.\\n\\nBut let us proceed. Search for these \"shrines\" and offer up the samples… then let's see what happens.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p9_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How can we learn more?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I don't know. Perhaps we collect samples from the creatures who've become Blighted? Yes, and then seek out another shrine.\\n\\nIt's worth a try at least. I wonder if there are shrines even in the midst of this? Let's find out.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p11_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What should I do?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Place your Azoth Staff in the water and step back. If this works, the staff should move in some way and point us in the general direction of the Motherwell.\\n\\nThat's my theory, at least.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p6v2_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Then what?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Then we follow the flow of azoth, and find out for ourselves if this Motherwell still exists.\\n\\nWe should inform Morgaine of what we've learned, if you'll find her, I'll figure out all the mapping parts.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Sun_p15_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You think Adiana was here, then too?",
        "NPCResponse": "Her voice is the same as that we heard at the Forest Shrines and the legends of the Huntress go far back.\\n\\nSo yes, I think it's quite likely that she is the same one, and that makes me nervous. Good luck.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She's just asking we proceed with caution.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Bah! In crises, caution can be foolish, but I'm willing to humor her. I trust she'll be joining us? Fine.\\n\\nBefore we proceed, however, I've discovered there are suspicious activities in this region, enemies of a different sort.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p1_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Myrddin's research on Edengrove.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "So my brother was here! I knew he ranged this far north, but I did not know he studied the Angry Earth! This is quite a revelation!\\n\\nI must take these notes where I can study them more carefully… you should talk to Sun.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p3_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Azoth? The blood of dead Ancients?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh my, that is... a rather outlandish proposition, but based on your earlier discovery, it makes sense. Myrddin must've known this.\\n\\nLook for samples of the veined stone that might be mined. Whatever's inside, we need it.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p4_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should activate it and find out.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "What do you think I've been doing here? Just humming a melody? The blasted thing is lacking an energy source.\\n\\nJust the kind of absurdity my brother so enjoyed… wait, but try using the crystals from the veined stones!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p5_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should go in and investigate.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, we must! But those damned Varangian raiders are already rummaging about… who knows how much they've already spoiled?!\\n\\nDestroy them, and carve a path for us to reach Myrddin's sanctum. We're so close now!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p8_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I hope we'll soon find out. \"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, let us solve this riddle, whatever it may bring. This looks similar to the Ancient prison device in the Fen, but Myrddin must've changed it.\\n\\nIt would seem to require the insertion of some item, something small.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p10_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Are you ready to see this through?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Honestly, I don't know. I have so many questions to ask, and the knowledge he has could turn the tide in the battle against Corruption.\\n\\nWe stand at the precipice of too many possibilities to consider. Let us go forward.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Morgaine_p10_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He accepted his fate.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "He may have accepted his fate, but that doesn't mean I have to! The fact he appeared at all proves there is some mechanism at work!\\n\\nI will liberate you from this madness, brother! I will not sleep until I do!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Galahad_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She believes this will help us fight Corruption.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "That would be a worthy outcome as well, but you should know the damned wizard's riddles are notoriously difficult.\\n\\nAll the same, let us venture into these towers and learn whatever we can. Lead on, Soulwarden.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Galahad_p3_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The key is close to the heart of those Myrddin loved…\"",
        "NPCResponse": "You mean… yes, of course! Artorius's shield was indeed held over his heart! \\n\\nLet us try this and find if it might be the solution to Myrddin's puzzle.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Galahad_p4a_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're not going in there, are you?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I am. Fare thee well, my friend. I could not have wished for a finer companion.\\n\\nI deeply regret I will not be at your side for the rest of your journey, but it is my first and foremost duty to find my lord king.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Myrddin_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need your help to stop her.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I am stuck here, but I offer this - the Staff of Wizardry, my staff, became Corrupted and was buried deep in the mines south of here.\\n\\nEven now, the Tempest seeks to reclaim it, and with it, all my power. You cannot allow this.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Adiana_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to cleanse the staff.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh… ? Is this why your polite friend visited previously and asked about the Motherwell?\\n\\nYou would seek my blessing to tap into the Angry Earth's most sacred source of power to cleanse a Wizard's bauble?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Yash_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, I need to find Yonas. Where is he?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "She… I mean that thing, that demon dragged him off towards the north gate.\\n\\nLet's go quickly… perhaps there is still time.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99E_Yash_p2_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There's still hope. Which way did they go?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I think they went west… I think, but I do not know. \\n\\nAfter I saw the darkness in her eyes, everything is very foggy in my memory… go after him, after Yonas, if you can. Please!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
